Jagan Mohan Bishoyi

Hard-working achiever, dedicated to on-time delivery, over 2 years of experience in developing web applications using various UI technologies. Designed over 30+ websites using bootstrap, wordpress and magento. Highly skilled in responsive design in lonic, Angular and Bootstrap. Next career goal is to become a full stack developer.

Garebhavipalya, Bangalore, 560068 (+91) 890-8348-100 jaganmohanbishoyi@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Sulopa Technology Pvt. Ltd., Bangalore — *Software Engineer*

APRIL 2019 - PRESENT

Sulopa Technology is a web based service providing company located in bangalore. There I served as a software engineer and my prime work is to develop and integrate UI with backend.

Sulopa Solution, Bangalore — *Software Engineer*

APRIL 2018 - APRIL 2019

Sulopa Solution is a web based service providing company located in bangalore. There I served as a software engineer and my prime work is to design static websites.

EDUCATION

GIIT, Berhampur — B.Tech(CSE)

AUGUST 2013 - IULY 2017

I completed my Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science in the year 2017 with 78%.

Binayak Acharya College, Berhampur — 12th Science

MARCH 2011 - MAY 2013

I completed my intermediate in the year 2013 with 53%.

RRBP High School, Chikiti — 10th

MAR 2009 - MAY 2010

I completed my matriculation in the year 2010 with 76%.

SKILLS

HTML5

CSS3

SCSS

Javascript

Jquery

Typescript

Angular 2+

Bootstrap

Ionic 4

Unit Testing

Git and GitLab

Wordpress

Magento2.0

Web Hosting

Shell Scripting

AWARDS

In NCAT(National Creativity Aptitude Test) 2014, I secured all India rank 61 in category 1.

In NCAT(National Creativity Aptitude Test) 2015, I secured all India rank 61 in category 2.

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi, Odia

HOBBIES

Reading and listening to books

Playing foosball and table tennis

Biking and Socializing

PROJECTS

Survey Application(PaaS)

Generally this application is about building project based questionnaires and taking online surveys of certain products and stores in the database.

Role: Frontend Developer / Team lead

Responsibilities:

- Development of web application by referring to Figma mockup.
- Designing the UI and binding it with the API
- Git Branching strategy and code merging

Technologies used: Angular 8, Node js

Periplus(Travel Management System)

Generally this application is about building itinerary and cost calculation, transport booking, hotel booking, travel agent booking

Role: Frontend Developer

Responsibilities:

- Development of web application.
- Designing the UI and binding it with the API

Technologies used: Angular 5, Node is

Micro Finance Platform

It is a micro-financing platform. It provides premium financial services to your everyday needs without any collateral requirements. Easy approval procedures with the shortest processing time will make the loan application simple and fast.

Role: Frontend Developer

Responsibilities:

- Development of web application.
- Converting mockup to html
- Designing the UI and binding it with the API

Technologies used: Angular 5, Node Js.

Menuadda (Restaurant Management System)

It is a Visual Menu for everyone, One stop solution for all restaurants. End to end restaurant management system which helps you manage and Increase the revenue for sure. We designed the admin dashboard using angular 7 and consumer application using Ionic 4.

Role: Team lead UI
Responsibilities:

- Planning for the development of application with team
- Development of web application.
- Converting mockup to html
- Designing the UI and binding it with the API

Technologies used: Angular 7, Ionic 4, Node Js, Serverless, Elastic search, Cloudinary image processing etc.

2mypalm (Asset Management System)

It is an asset management application. You can upload your document and asset details to organise your asset. It is worked as a reminder if an asset is going out of warranty. You can find the nearby service center for your asset or product. You can get service center addresses from integrated google maps.

Role: Frontend Developer
Technologies used: Ionic 3